Finding aid for the Bonnie Cashin Collection of Fashion, Theater, and Film Costume Design LSC.0440
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sills and Co. Ready-to-Wear, 1953 - 1977; 63 oversize boxes and 4 garment racks
  - Sketches (Sills and Co.), ca. 1950s-1975; 28 oversize boxes
    - Cashin's illustrations of poncho designs for Sills and Co., ca. 1953 - 1959; 14 illustrations (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's illustrations of Eastern-inspired outerwear for Sills and Co., ca. 1953 - 1959; 20 illustrations (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs, labeled "for Mennon" (Fitwell Dress Company)., May 1957; 3 illustrations (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., 1956 - 1958; 18 illustrations (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Cashin's illustrations of rainwear designs for Sills and Co., ca. 1960; 35 illustrations (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's illustrations of rainwear designs for Sills and Co., ca. 1960; 31 illustrations (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's illustrations of outerwear designs for Sills and Co., titled "Deep Freeze.", 1960; 5 illustrations (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., titled "Summer Somewhere.", 1960; 7 illustrations (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., Spring 1961; 6 illustrations (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1961; 31 illustrations (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1962; 14 illustrations (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1962; 15 illustrations (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's rough design illustrations and outlines of promotional ideas for Sills and Co., 1959; 17 pages (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1959; 16 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1960; 2 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., titled "Climate Control.", 1961; 5 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., titled "Omar the Tentmaker.", ca. 1962; 13 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1962; 2 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1963; 2 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1964; 4 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August - October 1965; 5 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., titled "Salute to Ernestine Carter.", ca. 1964; 6 illustrations (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1963; 23 illustrations (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1963; 10 illustrations (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., February 1963; 9 illustrations (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March 1963; 29 illustrations (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March 5 - 9, 1963; 18 illustrations (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., April 10, 1963; 2 illustrations (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1963; 8 illustrations (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1963; 12 illustrations (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1963; 17 illustrations (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1963; 18 illustrations (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1964; 21 illustrations (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., February 1964; 23 illustrations (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March 1964; 27 illustrations (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., April 1964; 6 illustrations (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., July 1964; 3 illustrations (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1964; 18 illustrations (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1964; 11 illustrations (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., titled "Salute to Ernestine Carter.", ca. 1964; 6 illustrations (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1964; 35 illustrations (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1965 and undated Ca. 1965; 25 illustrations (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1965; 31 illustrations (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1965; 27 illustrations (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1965; 16 illustrations (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1965; 20 illustrations (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September - October 1965; 20 illustrations (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1966; 28 illustrations (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1966; 28 illustrations (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1966; 9 illustrations (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1966; 19 illustrations (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1966; 30 illustrations (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1967; 18 illustrations (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., February 1967; 21 illustrations (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March 1967; 12 illustrations (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., April 1967; 16 illustrations (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1967; 6 illustrations (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1967; 9 illustrations (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1967; 8 illustrations (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., October 1967; 28 illustrations (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's illustration of a leather rag dress design for Sills and Co., ca. 1968; 1 illustration (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1968; 13 illustrations (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., February 1968; 25 illustrations (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March 1968; 26 illustrations (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., July - October 1968; 43 illustrations (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - February 1969; 27 illustrations (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March - July 1969; 21 illustrations (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August - September 1969; 12 illustrations (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 2 labeled for "Vogue.", ca. 1969; 28 illustrations (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 10 illustrations (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 11 illustrations (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 10 illustrations (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 11 illustrations (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's essays titled "Country Giving" and "Tree Trippers.", undated 1960s; 7 pages (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1961; 2 illustrations (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1961; 10 illustrations (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 25 illustrations (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 14 illustrations (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's rough illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 21 illustrations (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's rough ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., titled "Clothes to dance in" and "Rainy Day People.", ca. 1968; 2 illustrations (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1960s; 23 illustrations (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., ca. 1970 - 1971; 24 illustrations (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - February 1970; 40 illustrations (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1970; 30 illustrations (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - February 1971; 20 illustrations (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March - April 1971; 22 illustrations (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., June - September 1971; 31 illustrations (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - February 1972; 24 illustrations (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March 1972; 18 illustrations (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1972; 28 illustrations (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - March 1973; 36 illustrations (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., July - October 1973; 28 illustrations (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - July 1973; 5 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1974; 18 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., February 1974; 30 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March - July 1974; 26 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1974; 21 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1974; 17 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., October 1974; 13 illustrations (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January 1975; 16 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., February 1975; 15 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., March - July 1975; 21 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., August 1975; 24 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., September 1975; 12 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's illustrations of caftans designed for Sills and Co., 1975; 5 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., October 1975; 10 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., 1975 - 1976; 7 illustrations (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., Fall 1977; 24 illustrations (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's essay and fashion design illustrations featuring black models., Early 1970s; 6 pages (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., January - February 1974; 3 illustrations (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear design illustrations for Sills and Co., undated 1970s; 17 illustrations (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 30 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 30 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 30 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 30 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 30 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 28 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Photostats of Cashin's fashion design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 28 illustrations (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Photostats of Cashin design illustrations., ca. 1950s - 1960s; 21 illustrations (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's design of environmental hazard suit., ca. 1968; 1 illustration (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - Photostats of Sills Designs, ca. 1953 - 1972; 1 oversize box
    This subseries contains photostatic reproductions of Bonnie Cashin's designs illustrations for manufacturer Sills and Co. All materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Photostats of Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co. (copies of illustrations in boxes 36 - 39)., 1954 - 1972; 20 illustrations (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Photostats of Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co. (copies of illustrations in boxes 36 - 39)., ca. 1955 - 1960; 37 illustrations (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Photostats of Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co. (copies of illustrations in boxes 36 - 39)., ca. 1955 - 1965; 32 illustrations (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Photostats of Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., ca. 1955 - 1963; 37 illustrations (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Photostats of Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co. (copies of illustrations in boxes 36-39)., ca. 1953 - 1970; 35 illustrations (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - "Skirtings", ca. 1957 - 1961; 1 oversize box and 1 folder
    This subseries contains Bonnie Cashin's illustrations of skirt designs for "Skirtings," a division of Sills and Co. The subseries also contains promotional materials and photographs featuring the Skirtings collection. All illustrations by Bonnie Cashin contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Black and white photographs of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for "Skirtings", a division of Sills and Co., ca. 1957 - 1961; 10 photographs (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Portfolio for housing "Skirtings" design illustrations., 1957; 1 portfolio (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's promotional ideas for Skirtings collection., 1957; 2 pages (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's design illustrations with photostats., 1957; 22 illustrations (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's design illustrations with blurbs and swatches., 1957; 6 illustrations (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's design illustrations for June Havoc., ca. 1957; 2 illustrations (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's design illustrations., ca. 1957; 28 illustrations (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's design illustrations., ca. 1957; 27 illustrations (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Textile and Leather Swatches (Sills and Co. Ready-to-Wear), ca. 1975; 1 folder
    This subseries contains swatches of materials selected by Bonnie Cashin for use in her Ready-to-Wear designs.
    - Leather swatches for Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co.; colors named by Cashin., ca. 1975; 4 swatches (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Slides (Sills and Co. Ready-to-Wear), ca. 1955 - 1980; 3 oversize boxes
    This subseries contains slides of Bonnie Cashin's clothing design work. The subseries is particularly rich in slides of fashion shows and publicity photo shoots. Some materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in Cashin's home and the Sills and Co. showroom., 1958 - 1976; 25 slides (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in showroom., December 1964; 93 slides (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in showroom and workroom., ca. 1964 - 1965; 9 slides (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., Spring 1965; 9 slides (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., in workroom and Cashin's studio., November 1967 (Spring 1967 Collection); 38 slides (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in showroom., May 1967 (Fall 1967 Collection); 36 slides (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Fashion show and fittings of Cashin's ready-to-wear for Sills and Co., in showroom., November 1967 (Spring 1968); 34 slides (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Models in Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., backstage at showroom., May 1968 (Fall 1968 Collection); 13 slides (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in showroom., Spring 1969; 58 slides (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in workroom and showroom., Fall 1969; 26 slides (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., in showroom., February 1970 (Spring 1970); 69 slides (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in Cashin's apartment and studio., April 1970 (Fall 1970); 25 slides (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Models in Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., backstage at showroom., May 1970 (Fall 1970); 60 slides (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Cashin's illustrations of ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., 1970 - 1971; 11 slides (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in showroom and workroom., April - May 1971 (Fall 1971 Collection; 49 slides (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in Manhattan and in showroom / workroom., October 1971 (Spring 1972 Collection); 35 slides (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., modeled in showroom., January 1972 (Spring 1972 Collection); 30 slides (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co.; marked "All poor: keep as record only.", May 1972 (Fall 1972 show); 29 slides (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Models in Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., backstage at showroom., November 1972; 46 slides (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., in showroom., November 1973 (Spring 1974 Collection); 49 slides (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., November 1974 (Spring 1975); 13 slides (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Fashion show at Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., in showroom., May 1975; 13 slides (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., in showroom., June 1975; 104 slides (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co, modeled at Herman Miller showroom., November 1975; 72 slides (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., June 1977 (Fall 1977 Collection); 63 slides (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Fashion show of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., Fall 1977; 45 slides (Box 133, Folder 6)
      photographer: Helen O'Hagen
  - Fashion Show Commentary by Bonnie Cashin, ca. 1974 - 1978; 1 oversize box
    This subseries contains audio cassette recordings of Bonnie Cashin's commentary for her fashion shows. All recordings have been transferred to CD. All original recordings by Bonnie Cashin contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    SUBSERIES CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - Cassette recording: "Sills - opening Fall 1974"; reader copy on CD., May 1974; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Cassette recording: "Sills Spring Opening"; reader copy on CD., 1974 - 1975; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Cassette recording: "Sills Fall 1975"; reader copy on CD., May 1975; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - Cassette recording: "Sills Fall 1976"; reader copy on CD., May 1976; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Cassette recording: "Raincoats: Singing in the Rain"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1970s; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 17)
    - CD: "Raincoats: Singing in the Rain.", ca. 1970s; 1 CD (Box 242, Folder 47)
    - Cassette recording: "Gun Club Checks: The Entertainer"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1970s; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 18)
    - Cassette recording: "English and Macintosh: Colonel Bogey"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1970s; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 19)
    - Cassette recording: "Silver Bird"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1970s; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 20)
    - Cassette recording: "Pretty Prints: Autumn Leaves"; reader copy on CD., ca. 1970s; 1 audio cassette (Box 242, Folder 21)